Guide to the Department of Marketing and Communications records, 1997-2011.
Johnson Graduate School of Management Department of Marketing and Communications records, 1997-2011
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Johnson Graduate School of Management Department of Marketing and Communications records, 1997-2011.
26-9-3260
Johnson Graduate School of Management (Cornell University). Department of Marketing and Communications.
6.4 cubic ft.
Publicity material, photographs, reports, periodicals, plans, proposals, directories, and handbooks.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes publicity material, photographs, annual and placement reports, marketing periodicals, plans and proposals, directories and handbooks relating to the Johnson Graduate School of Management.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes publicity material, photographs, annual and placement reports, marketing periodicals, plans and proposals, directories and handbooks relating to the Johnson Graduate School of Management.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Johnson Graduate School of Management (Cornell University). Department of Marketing and Communications.; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University--Faculty.; Johnson Graduate School of Management (Cornell University)--Publicity.; Johnson Graduate School of Management (Cornell University)
Subjects:
Business schools--New York (State)--Ithaca; Management--Study and teaching--New York (State)--Ithaca.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
Videotapes.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Publicity Materials
Series II. Photographs
Series III. Ephemera
Series IV. Johnson Documents
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Publicity
  - Johnson Graduate School of Management, Early 1990's - 2003 (Box 1)
    Newsletters, flyers, brochures, posters, pamphlets, announcements
  - Johnson Graduate School of Management, Early 1990's - 2003 (Box 2)
  - Publicity booklet- Johnson Graduate School, ca. 1998 (Box 5)
  - Cornell Business newsletter, August 17, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Johnson Graduate School of Management, Early 1990's - 2004 (Box 6)
  - Johnson Graduate School - Newsletters, flyers, brochures, posters, pamphlets, including annual reports (2005-2011), 2004-2011 (Box 7)
  - 20th Anniversary Event (Box 19)
  - Admissions Brochure (Box 19)
  - Development Annual Giving (Box 19)
  - Binder (Box 19)
  - Enterprise Photos, Expression (Box 22)
  - Entrance, 1993 (Box 22)
  - Catalog Photos, 1993-1994 (Box 22)
  - Catalog Proposal, 1994 (Box 22)
  - Enterprise, 1994 (Box 22)
  - Enterprise Photos, 1990 (Box 22)
  - Classrooms (Box 22)
  - Campus Scenery (Box 22)
  - Enterprise Photos, 1992 (Box 22)
  - Hands (Box 22)
  - Meyer Computer Lab (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous Stuff (Box 22)
  - Catalogs, 1988-1995 (Box 22)
  - Executive Forum, 1982 (Box 22)
  - Reunion, 1986 (Box 22)
  - Japanese Program (Box 22)
  - Job Fairs (Box 22)
  - Old Ezra Reception, 1985-01 (Box 22)
  - Distinguished Alumni Speaker (Box 22)
  - Scholarship Recipients, 1994-1995 (Box 22)
  - Accelerated MBA Brochure (Box 22)
  - Admissions Envelopes (Box 22)
  - Park Brochure (Box 22)
  - Traditions brochure (Box 22)
  - Corporate Connections (Box 22)
  - JMB invite/postcard (Box 22)
  - Brand Folder (Box 23)
  - Note Cards (Box 23)
  - Military Student Brochure (Box 23)
  - Binder, 2004 (Box 23)
  - BRV (Big Red Ventures) Brochure (Box 23)
  - Chair Announcement (Box 23)
  - Corporate Connections (Box 23)
  - Cayuga Fund Brochure (Box 23)
  - Cayuga Fund Annual Report (Box 23)
  - Durland Lecture (Box 23)
  - Employment Report (Box 23)
  - Enterprise (Box 23)
  - Internship Brochure (Box 23)
  - JAC Brochure (Box 23)
  - Office of Diversity and inclusion (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
  - "Business of" events (Box 24)
  - Career Services (Box 24)
  - Corporate Partners (Box 24)
  - Cayuga Fund Brochure (Box 24)
  - Cayuga Fund Annual Report (Box 24)
  - Dean's Postcard (Box 24)
  - Honor Code brochure (Box 24)
  - European Symposium (Box 24)
  - Four Programs Brochure (Box 24)
  - MBA Program Comparison brochure (Box 24)
  - Hall of Honor, 2004 (Box 24)
  - Hall of Honor, 2007 (Box 24)
  - Immersion Brochure (Box 24)
  - Long-Range Plan (Box 24)
  - Math Brochure, 1997 (Box 24)
  - PhD brochure (Box 24)
  - Queens University (Box 24)
  - Johnson Annual Report (Box 24)
  - Brochure materials (Box 25)
  - Welcome to the Johnson School (Box 25)
  - Fall 2003-2005, 2003-2005 (Box 25)
  - Real Impact (Box 25)
  - Information Binders, 1999-2002 (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous continued (Box 26)
  - Recruiters Guide (Box 26)
  - Reunion Brochure (Box 26)
  - Sage Connection (Box 26)
  - Sage Hall brochure (Box 26)
  - Sage Hall Reprint (Box 26)
  - Search Piece (Box 26)
  - Staff Rewards and recognition program (Box 27)
  - State of the School (Box 27)
  - Twelve Month Option (Box 26)
  - Video (day in the life) (Box 26)
  - Viewbook (Box 26)
  - Financial Aid Booklet (Box 27)
  - Catalog 1996, 1996 (Box 27)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - Durland Lecture: Ann Fudge poster, 2005-04-06 (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Sage Hall History and Reconstruction Materials (Box subseries)
    - Not Just Another School of Business Administration: A History of Graduate Management Education at Cornell University by James W. Schmotter, 1992 (Box 29)
    - Jessie Boulton Letters from Cornell University 1879-1883 (typed, bound collection) (Box 29)
    - Sage Hall reconstruction project: The 1999 Business Week Architectural Record Awards (application booklet/docs), 1999 (Box 29)
    - Sage Hall in the 60s by Benson J. Simon AB '61, MBA '62 (annotated photographs), 1958, 1961-1962 (Box 29)
    - Malott Hall photo album, includes Follies, candids, and class photos for 1950, 1956, 1957. Faculty photos of Hal Bierman teaching in 1956, 1950, 1956-1957 (Box 29)
    - Sage Hall background folder includes "Sage College - Language of Cornerstone (May 1873); Sage Hall dedication brochure, Oct. 2-3, 1998; Buildinbg the Future (campaign booklet for Sage Hall renovation (1994); bookchapter VI, The Early Years," from A History of Cornell, other docs (Box 29)
    - Sage Hall architectural floor plans (Mapcase-folder 1)
    - Sage Hall history and dedication documents - thick file folders of articles, interviews, brochure copy/info
    - Notes on the Sage College/Hall Exhibiti for JGSM, June 20-Aug. 27, 1997, 1997 (Box 29)
    - Sage Hall Renovation - Beacon Skanska Construction Co. AON award application booklet (Box 29)
    - Sage Hall reconstruction photos (color prints) including installing Sage Hall's spire; interior shots of the job in progress (Jon Reis), 1997; and black and white exterior shots, 1997 (Jon Reis), 1997 (Box 29)
    - "Outdoor scenes" folder of misc. photos: Cornell Plantations; Ithaca Commons; gorges/waterfalls; sailboats on Cayuga Lake; Cornell campus; Arts Quad; Law School (Box 29)
    - Black and White photos of bell tower, Comstock Hall (Box 29)
    - Outdoor scenes, Ithaca (Box 29)
    - Outdoor scenes - Cornell folder (Box 29)
    - photo of McGraw Hall, Johnson Art Museum (Box 29)
    - Sage Hall renovation, before and during (slides) (Box 29)
    - Sage Hall, before and after reconstruction - misc. photos (prints) (Box 29)
    - Sage Hall images (architect's renderings, pre-reconstruction); illustration (greeting card); articles (Box 29)
    - Sage Hall Cornerstone Celebration 1997 brochure text), 1997 (Box 29)
    - Sage Hall photos and renderings (Box 27)
    - Sage Hall atrium 4x5 transparencies (U Photo, 2000), 2000 (Box 29)
    - Johnson School mission statements, 1995: drafts from Acting Dean Thomas R. Dyckman; correspondence, 1995 (Box 29)
    - State of the School - Johnson Graduate School of Management, Feb. 18, 1999 (Dean Robert J. Swieringa; President Hunter Rawlings, 1999 (Box 29)
    - Dean Swieringa's speech to the Ithaca Rotary Club, July 7, 1999, 1999 (Box 29)
    - Sage Hall pre-construction file, includes renderings (transpaerencies), photos (prints), floor plans, interior shot pre-reconstruction, 1996-07-30 (Box 29)
    - Johnson family, Johnson School, Sage Hall articles (Box 29)
    - Johnson history in the History of Higher Education Annual: "The Best Emissaries": MBA Students at Cornell University, 1948-1987 by James W. Schmotter (Box 29)
- Series II. Photographs
  - Guest Speakers; A-D (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Guest Speakers; E-H (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Guest Speakers; I-K (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Guest Speakers; L (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Guest Speakers; M (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Guest Speakers; N-P (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Guest Speakers; R (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Guest Speakers; S (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Guest Speakers; S (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Guest Speakers; S (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Guest Speakers; T-W (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Guest Speakers; W (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Class Speakers, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Class Speakers-Stan Smith's Class (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
  - EDP, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - EDP, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - EDP, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - EDP, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - EDP, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - EDP, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - EDP, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - EDP Summer, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - EDP Summer, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Executive Authors (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Executive; Harold Green; David Hourer (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Executive Interviews; Irving Kristol; Thomas Murphy; Roy Park; David Rockefeller; James Schlesinger; Lewis Thomas; Gustavo Vollmer; Walter Wriston (Box 3, Folder 27-30)
  - Executive Photos-Foreign Products (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Alumni Group Shots (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Alumni Executive Council; AEC Mtg. 1989; AEC Mtg. April 88 NYC; AEC Mtg. May 1987; AEC Mtg. July 1986; AEC Photos May 85; AEC Mtg. Nov. 1984, 1984-1989 (Box 3, Folder 33-37)
  - Alumni/Johnson School Rochester Club (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Annual Fund; CGSM Fund (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Class and Club Officers Meetings; Class and Officers Mtg. Feb. 21-22, 1991; Class and Club Officers Mtg. May 1987; AEC Mtg. Sept. 15, 1989; Class and Club Officers Mtg. Sept. 8, 1988, 1987-1981 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - JGSM Clubs; 1986: JGSM Club of New York City; Washington Club, 1987-1981 (Box 3, Folder 41-42)
  - Best Business Schools (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Career Services Job Fair; Job Fair, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Classroom Shots; Ben Daniels' Entrepreneur Class Lectures; Oral & Written Communications; Classroom shots-various; Ethics Dilemmas in Management Course 1984; Classroom 1984; Classroom shots 1987-88, 1984-1988 (Box 3, Folder 45-50)
  - Commencement, 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Follies, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Japanese Student Interns (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Pre-Tower Club Dinner, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Recruiting, 1984, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Sports scenes; basketball, various, intramural, hockey game-faculty and students, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 7-9)
  - Professors and Students (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Sound Investments, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Student Groups, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Student Groups, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Student Groups, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Student Groups, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Student Groups, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Student Groups, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Student Groups, Spring, Fall, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Student Groups, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Student Groups, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Student Groups, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Student Groups, 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Student Groups, 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 23-28)
  - Student Groups, 1960s (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Student Presentations (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Summer Internships, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Malott Resources - Computers, VAX Facility, Meyer Computing Lab (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Johnson School Library; JGSM Library; B & PA Library-Old Photos; Malott Library-New Optical Disk; GSM Libe-recent photos (Box 4, Folder 33-34)
  - Art Gallery (Box 4, Folder 35-40)
  - Hall of Honor; B & PA Hall of Honor; Miscellaneous; Hall of Honor-Schaenen (Box 4, Folder 41-46)
  - Mallot Hall; Mallot-inside; Mallot new wing dedication (Box 4, Folder 47-51)
  - At Play (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Public Program Photos (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Willard Straight Hall Reading Room (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Reunion, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 55-58)
  - Reunion, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Reunion, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
  - Reunion, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Reunion, Gerald R. Ford, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 5-7)
  - Reunion, Henry Kissinger, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 8-10)
  - Reunion, William F. Buckley, Sloan Dinner, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 11-15)
  - Reunion, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 16-19)
  - Brussels 86; Paris 87, London 88, Brussels 89, The Johnson School's First Asian Program Tokyo 89, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 20-25)
  - Reunion, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 26-29)
  - Reunion, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 30-31)
  - Students; Soviet Visitors, Frozen Assets, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Students; April Hosting Program, JGSM Placement and Recruiters Guide, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Students; April Hosting Program, JGSM Placement and Recruiters Guide, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Student Portraits (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Former Staff, Faculty, Students
    - Adair, Wendi (Box 8)
    - Allen, Randy (Box 8)
    - Alumni featured in Entreprise (Box 9)
    - Bailey, Warren B. (Box 8)
    - Barrett, Craig (Box 10)
    - BenDaniel, David J. (Box 8)
    - Bhojraj, Sanjeev (Box 8)
    - Bierman JR., Harold (Box 8)
    - Bloomfield, Robert J. (Box 8)
    - Botti, Simona (Box 8)
    - Bradley, James R. (Box 8)
    - Brinckman. Jan (Box 8)
    - Conway, Richard W. (Box 8)
    - Curtis, Rich (Box 8)
    - D'Souza, Julia (Box 8)
    - Dyckman, Thomas R. (Box 8)
    - Eisenstein, Eric (Box 8)
    - Elliot, John A. (Box 8)
    - Faculty (Box 13)
    - Faculty Groups, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Faculty A-F (Box 18)
    - Faculty G-M (Box 18)
    - Faculty N-S (8 folders) (Box 18)
    - Faculty T-Z (3 folders) (Box 18)
    - Farahat, Amr (Box 8)
    - Farewell, Corine (Box 8)
    - Fields, Tom (Box 8)
    - Frank, Robert H. (Box 8)
    - Gadiesh, Orit (Box 10)
    - Gavirneni, Srinagesh (Box 8)
    - Gomez, Miguel (Box 8)
    - Greenberg, Donald P. (Box 8)
    - Grinstein, Yaniv (Box 8)
    - Gupta, Sachin (Box 8)
    - Hart, Stuart (Box 8)
    - Hass, Jerome E. (Box 8)
    - Heffetz, Ori (Box 8)
    - Hilton, Ronald W. (Box 8)
    - Hochberg, Yael (Box 8)
    - Hostetler, Michael (Box 8)
    - Hribar, S. Paul (Box 8)
    - Huang, Ming (Box 8)
    - Iankova, Elena (Box 8)
    - Isen, Alice M. (Box 8)
    - Janosi, Tibor (Box 8)
    - Jarrow, Robert A. (Box 8)
    - Johnson, Justin (Box 8)
    - Johnson, Sam (Box 8)
    - Juran, David (Box 8)
    - Kadiyali, Vrinda (Box 8)
    - Katz, Jan H. (Box 8)
    - Kraft, Walter (Box 8)
    - Kumar, Pankaj (Box 8)
    - Lee, Angela (Box 8)
    - Lee, Charles M.C. (Box 8)
    - Li, Haitao (Box 8)
    - Libby, Robert (Box 8)
    - Lind, Robert C. (Box 8)
    - Mannix, Elizabeth (Box 8)
    - McClain, John O. (Box 8)
    - McAdams, Alan K. (Box 8)
    - Michaely, Roni (Box 8)
    - Milstein, Mark (Box 8)
    - Mink, Barbara E. (Box 8)
    - Nelsen, Bonalyn J. (Box 8)
    - Nelson, Mark W. (Box 8)
    - Nichols, D. Craig (Box 8)
    - Noble-Grange, Angela (Box 8)
    - Nozell, John (Box 8)
    - O'Connor, Kathleen M. (Box 9)
    - O'Hara, Maureen (Box 9)
    - Orman, Levent (Box 9)
    - Park, Young-Hoon (Box 9)
    - Peterson, Randall S. (Box 9)
    - PhD students (Box 9)
    - Pike, Alan S. (Box 9)
    - Rao, Vithala R. (Box 9)
    - Radcliffe, Dana (Box 9)
    - Reyes, Jesse (Box 9)
    - Robinson, Lawrence W. (Box 9)
    - Rosen, Charlotte J. (Box 9)
    - Russo, J. Edward (Box 9)
    - Saar, Gideon (Box 9)
    - Sally, David F. (Box 9)
    - Sapra, Amar (Box 9)
    - Schneider, George (Box 9)
    - Schultz, Kenneth (Box 9)
    - Shulman, Zachary (Box 9)
    - Sidle, Clint (Box 9)
    - Sine, Wesley (Box 9)
    - Smidt, Seymour (Box 9)
    - Spataro, Sandra (Box 9)
    - Staff (Box 9)
    - Staff Photos A-K (Box 15)
    - Staff Photos L-Z (Box 15)
    - Stayman, Douglas M. (Box 9)
    - Sunder (Box 9)
    - Suwinski, Jan H. (Box 9)
    - Swaminathan, Bhaskaran (Box 9)
    - Swieringa, Robert J. (Box 9)
    - Szpiro, Danny (Box 9)
    - Tettlebaum, Josh (Box 9)
    - Thomas, L. Joseph (Box 9)
    - Thomas-Hunt, Melissa (Box 9)
    - Tookes, Heather (Box 9)
    - Or, C. Annique (Box 9)
    - Vierd, Marie Louise (Box 9)
    - Visiting Professors (Box 9)
    - Waldman, Michael (Box 9)
    - Weinbaum, David (Box 9)
    - Yehuda, Air (Box 9)
    - Zhang, Rachel (Box 9)
    - Zhang, Xiaoyan (Box 9)
    - Zurack, Mark (Box 9)
    - Admissions Dept. Pictures, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Career services dept. pictures, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Dean's office pictures, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Executive educ dept pictures, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Class pictures, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Student Classroom shots, Date Unknown (Box 13)
    - Marketing Dept. Pictures, Date Unknown (Box 13)
    - Registrar/Financial aid pictures, Date Unknown (Box 13)
    - Student activities pictures, Date Unknown (Box 13)
    - Technology services pictures, Date Unknown (Box 13)
    - Library Dept Pictures, Date Unknown (Box 13)
    - Staff A-M - Tom Duckman, Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Staff N-Z - Peters, Harriet; Schmotter, Jim; Don S., Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Former Staff, Date Unknown (Box 18)
  - Alumni
    - Alumni Classes '07 '02 '03 '04 '05 (Box 13)
    - Alumni A-M (Box 18)
    - Alumni "Abelson-Atkins (Box 20)
    - Alumni "Baker -Bisha" (Box 20)
    - Alumni "Black-Burmeister" (Box 20)
    - Alumni "Cahill-Currier" (Box 20)
    - Alumni "Darby-Dyson" (Box 20)
    - Alumni "Eastman-Estabrook" (Box 20)
    - Alumni "Falkon-Friedberg" (Box 20)
    - Alumni "Gabler-Gorman" (Box 20)
    - Alumni "Grace-Gwynn" (Box 20)
    - Alumni "Hahn-Hutterly" (Box 20)
    - Alumni "I" (Box 20)
    - Alumni "Jackman-Junger" (Box 20)
    - Alumni "Kaplan-Klotz (Box 20)
    - Alumni "Knaugs-Krause" (Box 21)
    - Alumni "Labick - Lynch" (Box 21)
    - Alumni "Mansoor-Murphy" (Box 21)
    - Alumni N-Z (Box 18)
    - Alumni "Naert-Noto" (Box 21)
    - Alumni "O'Hara-Otis" (Box 21)
    - Alumni "Park Provencher" (Box 21)
    - Alumni "Q" (Box 22)
    - Alumni "Rabatin-Pussel" (Box 21)
    - Alumni "Sheldon-Sung" (Box 21)
    - Alumni "Sacra-Singhal" (Box 21)
    - Alumni T-Z (Box 18)
    - Alumni " Talmon-Tsurada" (Box 21)
    - Alumni "V" (Box 21)
    - Alumni "Wadell-Wolf" (Box 21)
    - Alumni "Yamamoto-Young" (Box 21)
    - Alumni "Z" (Box 21)
  - Students and Student Groups
    - Student Groups, 1985-1987 (Box 16)
    - Student Portraits, 1987-1988 (Box 18)
    - Student Groups, 1988-03-1988-05 (Box 18)
    - Student Groups, 1988-09-1988-11 (Box 18)
    - Student Groups, 1988-1993 (Box 17)
    - Student Portraits 90 (5 folders), 1990 (Box 17)
    - Student Portraits 91-92 (3 folders), 1991-1992 (Box 16)
    - Student Groups with Dean Merten, 1991 (Box 17)
    - Graduating Class photos, 1991-1997 (Mapcase-folder 1)
    - Student Portraits, 1992 (Box 17)
    - Students, 1993-1997 (Box 11)
    - Student Portraits, 1999-2001 (Box 16)
    - Student Stock Photos, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Student Photos, 2000-09 (Box 10)
    - Student Portraits, 2002-2003 (Box 14)
    - Student Stock Photos, 2004 (Box 15)
    - Student Photos, 2005 (Box 16)
    - Assorted Student Groups, Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Park Fellow Portraits, Date Unknown (Box 15)
    - Doctoral Students, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Students, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - External Relations Pictures, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Faculty Support Dept. Pictures, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Johnson Custodians Pictures, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Business Office pictures, Date Unknown (Box 12)
  - Photographs by date
    - Executive Forum, 1975-1981 (Box 17)
    - Public Colloquium, 1978-1980 (Box 18)
    - Energy Seminar 1981, 1981 (Box 17)
    - Ads Spring 1982, 1982 (Box 19)
    - Executive Forum 1983-1985 (3 folders), 1983-1985 (Box 16)
    - EYP 1984-1989, 1984-1989 (Box 17)
    - Phonathon 1984-1985, 1984-1985 (Box 17)
    - Japan US Trade Conference, 1985-04 (Box 19)
    - Speakers - Richard Ferris 1986, 1986 (Box 16)
    - Leven 1986, 1986 (Box 17)
    - International Reunion Paris 1987, 1987 (Box 17)
    - Doctoral Program Brochure Student Photos 87-88, 1987-1988 (Box 11)
    - Follies 1987, 1987 (Box 18)
    - Partners Day '87, 1987 (Box 18)
    - Black Executives spring 88, 1988 (Box 17)
    - Lifelong Learning program 5/1988, 1988-05 (Box 18)
    - Hockey 1988 (2 slides), 1988 (Box 19)
    - photos of a book (depicting McGraw tower, Cornell) 1988 (2 slides), 1988 (Box 19)
    - Umbrella Shots 89, 1989 (Box 17)
    - Johnson Portrait Unveiling 10/89, 1989-10 (Box 17)
    - Campaign celebration dinner 10/2/89, 1989-10-02 (Box 16)
    - International Business Association 90-91, 1990-1991 (Box 17)
    - Catalog 1990-91, 1990-1991 (Box 18)
    - Dean's Merton's talk 1990, 1990 (Box 19)
    - Russian Visitors 91, 1991 (Box 17)
    - Commencement 1992, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Catalog 92-96: color transparencies, 1992-1996 (Box 17)
    - Catalog 92-93, 1992-1992 (Box 17)
    - Orientation Class of 93, 1993 (Box 11)
    - Ryan Reception April 17, 1993, 1993-04-17 (Box 12)
    - London 1993, 1993 (Box 12)
    - Fundraising development - campus visit 1993, 1993 (Box 16)
    - Guest Speakers 93-94 - Derivative Securities, 1993-1994 (Box 17)
    - Student Activities 93-94 - Frozen Assets, 1993-1994 (Box 17)
    - Student Activities 93-94 - Women's Management Council, 1993-1994 (Box 17)
    - Student Phonathon Fall 94 & 95, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
    - Johnson School Programs 1994-95, 1994-1995 (Box 13)
    - Johnson School Activities 94-95, 1994-1995 (Box 13)
    - Career Forum, 1994-1995 (Box 13)
    - Campaign Brochure 1994, 1994 (Box 17)
    - Career Forum 94-95, 1994-1995 (Box 19)
    - Catalog 95-96, 1995-1996 (Box 17)
    - Fried Fellows 95-96, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - Levy Fellows '95-'96, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - Scientist as manager - NYC roundtable discussion, 1995-10-18 (Box 11)
    - Releases '95-'96, 1995-1996 (Box 12)
    - Fall '95 Phonathon, 1995-09-1995-11 (Box 16)
    - Twelve month option Aug 96, 1996 (Box 12)
    - Facebook files 96-97, 1996-1997 (Box 12)
    - 1997 Graduation, 1997 (Box 11)
    - Fried Fellows 1997, 1997 (Box 11)
    - 1997-98 Fried Fellows, 1997-1998 (Box 11)
    - Releases '97-'98, 1997-1998 (Box 12)
    - Student Faculty Committee 97-98, 1997-1998 (Box 12)
    - Park Fellows 1997, 1997 (Box 16)
    - Enterprise Spring '97, 1997 (Box 16)
    - Durland Lecture, 1998 (Box 9)
    - Abbey Cohen '98, 1998 (Box 9)
    - #8 Party, 1998, 1998 (Box 9)
    - Johnson School 1998 - History, 1998 (Box 10)
    - Durland '98, 1998 (Box 11)
    - 1998 Hatfield Lecture, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Walk on Wall Street 1998, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Trustee Dinner 1998, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Class of '98, 1998 (Box 12)
    - Releases '98-'99, 1998-1999 (Box 12)
    - Golf tournatment 1998, 1998 (Box 12)
    - Park Speaker Rod Chy 9/3/98, 1998-09-03 (Box 12)
    - Assorted Johnson school photos, 1999 (Box 29)
    - Graduation 1999, 1999 (Box 9)
    - MGBA 1999, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Rocca '99, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Coffee Hour, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Orientation, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Beer Game Photos, 1999 (Box 11)
    - M&A Symposium, 1999-10-29 (Box 11)
    - Irene Rosenfeld, 1999-03 (Box 12)
    - Cornell Equity Research, 1999 (Box 12)
    - Durland Lecture, 1999-04 (Box 12)
    - European Symposium, 1999-03 (Box 12)
    - Randall Peterson, 1999-04 (Box 12)
    - Doug Stayman, 1999-01 (Box 12)
    - Staff Recognition Luncheon, 1999-05-20 (Box 13)
    - Technology Symposium 1999, 1999 (Box 13)
    - State of the School, 1999-02-18 (Box 13)
    - Destination Johnson 2000, 2000 (Box 12)